I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Hey! Ryusuke! Are you home?
I'll take that vocalist position!
He's...ready to do it now?
Hey! Ryusuke-chan!
He's feeling good...
And...
I wanna make friends with a girl like this!
"Saito Paper Company"
What do you think?!
That song...What was it?
It was "Sunshine" by the Rocket Boys.
Let me see your hand.
-Nope...Not yet.
-Huh?
You've just started.
Fool!
Koyuki-kun!
"25th Annual Sekikawa Hometown Festival"
"Singing Contest"
Tadah!
"25th Annual Sekikawa Hometown Festival"
"Singing Contest"
A singing contest?
"25th Annual Sekikawa Hometown Festival"
"Singing Contest"
To tell you the truth, things got
exciting at our last class reunion.
My old band members and I
decided to get together again!
You mean you're going
to enter the contest?
Yeah! I registered your name
as a member, too!
Huh?! Me, a member?!
You'll improve faster
if you have a concrete goal.
But I just got started...
We'll be playing "Follow Me"
by my favorite band, the Rocket Boys.
Fool!
One, two...
Follow me
Baby, I won't let you leave
if you believe in me
And I always set you free
from all those yesteryears
But you don't know how much
I got believe in you
I was staring at your shoulder shivering
in such a coldest summer breeze
Meanwhile, I wonder why we're here
Look for the line
between love and friends
We'll be twisting ourselves again
I was standing at
the corner on the street
Watching the wheels are turning free
waiting to back up on my-
I'm sorry!
Shall we take a break?
No...I'm fine!
We have to perform soon...
I'll do my best!
Koyuki-kun...You need
a change of pace sometimes.
That's right.
What are you doing, you blockhead?!
Your kick's no good at all!
Okay! Five more laps!
B-but...
You, over there...
Don't hang onto the rope.
Raise your pitch! You dumbbell!
This summer, for some reason,
I learned to do the butterfly kick.
This fishing hole...
You sure there are fish here?
Yeah...
-These are Chiba's?
-Yes. That's right.
Really? I didn't realize
he listened to this kind of music.
No, ever since he decided to
join the band, he's been studying up.
But they're all hip hop. You know...
Well, he's trying his best.
Say...Have you thought
of a name for the band?
Huh?
I guess that's about it.
"MRG (Minami Ryusuke's Group)
Minami Ryusuke Band
R.E.M. (Ryusuke "Eminent" Minami)
Minami Ryusuke & Family
Minami Ryusuke Orchestra"
Why is it you're always...
so self-centered?!
I am the one starting up the band.
Then you decide on the band name, Chiba.
Beck!
Huh?
Let's go with Beck!
Beck?
Then...Wouldn't Blue Lightning be good?
Naked Devils? Or how
about Dream Travelers?
What do you think?!
Looks like today's contest
will probably be canceled.
"Contest!"
Maybe I should do my homework...
Who's there?!
Koyuki!
M-Maho-chan...
I'm all wet. Let me in, will you?
Huh?! "Let me in"?
I'm sorry for barging in on you.
It's okay, but how did
you know where I lived?
Ryusuke told me when
we passed by the other day.
"Koyuki plays that guitar like
he's trying hard to chase each chord."
"There's no feeling."
"The most important thing is wanting
to convey something to others."
Huh? Convey something?
That's what Ryusuke said as
he listened to you playing.
Ryusuke-kun said that?
Ah, that felt good! Thanks, Koyuki!
Sure...
Koyuki...Shouldn't you
get ready for the contest?
Yeah...
"Sekikawa Hometown Festival"
Don't get so tense, Koyuki-kun!
It's only a neighborhood contest!
You shouldn't be drinking so much.
Oh, Maho-chan. This is
our drummer, Horiuchi-san.
Glad to meet you.
Nice to meet you. I play the drums, yes.
This is our vocalist and bassist,
Kamejima-san.
Kamejima-san!
K-Kame-yan! Kame-yan!
Wha?! Hic!
Kamejima-san! Can you hear me?
We're going now.
Let's go!
-I'd like you to come too.
-Kamejima-san...
Who, me?!
We're going to win!
Huh?
We've come back together again
after all these years!
For Kame-yan's sake, we'll win!
But...Saito-san went
with the ambulance...
Then I'll sing!
-Huh?!
You're serious?
Yeah!
The prize for this contest is a trip
to Southeast Asia...Quite fancy!
Oh, that. It was a request from the
son of the neighborhood chairman.
Oh, really? Isn't the guy
singing right now-
Yeah. That's the chairman's
good-for-nothing son.
So you mean the contest is fixed?
Probably. Oh, this is
off the record, by the way.
Oh, boy...
By the way, is Yat-chan well?
Yeah. He's gonna be 24 this year.
Oh? No wonder we're getting old.
A fixed contest?
Wow!
You won't know unless you give it a try!
But...I heard it clearly!
We'll change the minds
of the judges with our music!
That's impossible...
Doesn't it make you mad, Koyuki?!
Sure it does!
But it's how the world works...
-We will win!
-Okay! Let's make a bet!
The loser...has to get naked!
Yeah! I've been waiting for this!
So cute...
Koyuki!
There are some lines I'm not sure of.
Sing with me, will you?
Follow me
Baby, I won't let you leave
if you believe in me
And I always set you free
from all those yesteryears
But you don't know how much
I got believe in you
I was staring at your shoulder shivering
in such a coldest summer breeze
Meanwhile, I wonder why we're here
Look for the line
between love and friends
We'll be twisting ourselves again
I was standing
at the corner on the street
Watching the wheels are turning free
waiting to back up on my feet
"Emcee" "Judge"
-Reading a line
-between night and day
-I'll be twisting myself
again
That's Tanaka's lucky No. 55 T-shirt!
-Follow me
-(Follow me)
-Baby, I won't let you leave
if you believe in me
-(Believe in me)
-And I always set you free
from all those yesteryears
-(Believe in me)
But you don't know how much
-Follow me
-Baby, I won't let you leave
-if you believe in me
-And I always set you free-
Here are the results!
This year's winner is...
(Koyuki!)
(Maho!)
Koyuki...Hurry! Hurry!
We shouldn't, Maho-chan!
"Do not use school facilities without-"
Koyuki!
Maho...
Yay!
Wow! This feels great!
M-Maho...You're too loud!
What if someone sees?!
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day...
I was fool
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Old love affair
Floating like a bird resting her wings
Koyuki?
Here goes!
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day...
On my way
Looking for a moment with my dear
Full moon waves
Slowly on the surface of the lake
You were there
Smiling in my arms for all those years
-What a fool
-I don't know 'bout tomorrow
-What it's like to be
-Ah...
-I was fool
-Couldn't let myself to go
-Even though I feel
-The end
Old love affair
Floating like a bird resting her wings
You were there
Smiling in my arms for all those years
-What a fool
-I don't know 'bout tomorrow
-What it's like to be
-Ah...
-I was fool
-Couldn't let myself to go
-Even though I feel
-The end
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day...
You were there
Smiling in my arms for all those years
Observe!
I punched the lights out of the boy
who won, and took this away!
"Southeast Asia Tour"
Next week, Kame-yan and I
are going on a tour!
"Southeast Asia Tour"
Summer vacation is over now!
-What?! That's not fair!
Don't you owe it to us?!
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
80 yen in my pocket...
I don't get paid for three more days.
"Next Episode"
"Hyodo and the Jaguar"
I don't get paid for three more days.
"Next Episode"
"Hyodo and the Jaguar"